<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Putschko &#43; R</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Putschko &#43; R</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidy Tuesday - 19 March 2019</title>
      <link>/2019/03/21/tidy-tuesday-19-march-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/21/tidy-tuesday-19-march-2019/</guid>
      <description>The data this week relates to law enforcement traffic stops from around the US. The data was compiled by Stanford University. Find more information on the Tidy Tuesday page.
I’m going to spend only a couple hours putting this blog post, in the hopes of developing both my writing and my data viz skills. I hope to repeat this process either every week or a couple times per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Profiling</title>
      <link>/2019/03/06/data-profiling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/06/data-profiling/</guid>
      <description>When I’m starting a new project, I typically have no idea what is present in a data set, and I don’t know enough about the project to formulate reasonable questions for the keepers of the data. So I’m usually running an identical set of processes on every new data set I come across.
I’ve discovered the DataExplorer package for R recently, which aims to assist in this process of shining a light into the cavern of unknown data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Resources</title>
      <link>/2019/01/28/data-science-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/28/data-science-resources/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using R since 2013. In those days, R information was hard to come by. Information and best practices that did exist were kept under heavy guard. Most requests for help online were met with gate-keeping responses such as, “Did you read the help file?” or the classic, “Hey, I have a question”, followed by, “Never mind, I solved it - please delete”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>/2019/01/25/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/25/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Stay tuned!
This is the first post of my blog! Here I will discuss my adventures into the world of Data Science and R.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>